(Previously) Take your troops there.
Detain all the key royals as leverage.
The target we are hunting...
Let me see Phob.
If they break in, shoot them all down.
Phob...
Go to hell, Phob!
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Phob...
Your Phob is right here.
And I will never leave your side again.
Captain Phobthee! May I ask
what official business brings you here?
Even without official business,
perhaps I came simply because I missed him.
"The Edge of Horizon"
(Episode 6)
This is profit from your first mining
business' investment, Your Highness.
I got this much profit
from the first month?
I think it's because of your luck.
I am hesitating if I should
invest some more.
I want to gain more profit.
You would be stupid if
you didn't invest more.
Here, put this money into my share
and I will find more to invest.
I still have money from
the ministry's budget.
Oh wow!
You're so brilliant.
I can guarantee you that by June,
we both will be so wealthy.
Come on, cheers!
Everyone will finally realize
that I didn't have to do well
in school like Tin and Phob,
still I can make more money than they can.
And my dad will finally praise me.
Let's cheers again!
Let's get rich!
You used work as an excuse
to be around my son all the time.
If that's the case, what are
you going to do about it?
Phob!
You need to stop being
around Thinakorn already.
Let him go.
I am not a servant in your palace.
I don’t have to do what you say.
Also,
Prine Thinakorn
risked his life to save mine.
He was so brave to save me.
You can't expect me to
leave him just like that.
Chat?
Whose car is this?
This is my car, Grandma.
I invested in a mining
business with my friend.
I thought that I'd buy a small car but...
I made a lot of profit so I decided to
buy the same model and color as my dad's.
Wonderful.
This is for you.
For me?
- That's right.
- Thanks, honey.
Thank you so much. I wish you
big success in your business.
- Thank you. Hey, Aum.
- Yes?
Tell the servants to meet
me in the main building.
I have some gifts for everyone.
Sure, Your Highness. Thank you.
Well done.
Dad?
I have invested
in a mining business with my friends
and I made a lot of profit.
So I bought a new car,
it is the same model and
the same color as yours.
Isn't she pretty?
Are you sure that it is from
the business investment?
It wasn't from your gambling money?
Don't drag us to your problems.
Vasin,
don't be too harsh on him,
okay?
- Aum?
- Yes, Your Highness.
If Thinakorn is here, tell him to see me.
Yes, Your Highness.
My dad has never cared about me.
He has never praised me,
he only cares about Thinakorn.
Come on, don't be sad.
He just came back from work,
he must be exhausted.
Okay?
Grandma, you have to see it.
I will make a lot of money
and I will show my dad
that I can do well in my life.
I will bring a good reputation to the family.
I will, I can't wait to see it.
I wish your dream comes true.
- I love you the most.
- I love you, too.
Let's try it on. I want to see it.
Aum told me that you wanted to see me.
Is everything okay?
Have a seat.
My colleague's nephew came back
from England last week.
I am looking for the right job for him.
I think this is a good opportunity
that he can replace you at work.
What do you mean?
You need to resign,
and stay home,
while I look for
a new position for you.
A new position?
A new position where I don't have to be
involved with Phobthee?
That's right.
Why are you doing this?
You need to ask yourself.
You took a bullet for him.
You wanted me to let
Chat shoot him to death?
Thinakorn,
you know the real reason why you saved him.
It wasn't because of humanity.
But it was because you didn't forget him.
You should have forgotten all about him.
You should have stopped loving him
or thinking about him.
You need to protect the family's honor.
The family's honor?
Why does the family's honor
feel so heavy on my shoulders?
I can't even
think about him
- or keep him in my memories.
- Tin!
Actually, if you want me
to forget all about this,
there is another way.
What is it?
You can just kill me.
Thinakorn!
My prince, where are you?
Where are you?
Are you here?
My prince, where are you?
There you are! I found you!
Oh my! You found me!
No matter where you are
I will always find you.
Phob.
Your Highness.
Oh my gosh!
You don't like it?
It's too cold.
I saw you working hard
so I brought you some water,
to freshen you up.
Thank you.
Is it cold enough?
Hey! Phob!
Oh, it's staying.
Hey!
Give me your money!
Hurry up, you want to die?
Phob!
- Hey!
- Phob!
Watch out!
Let's go, hurry!
Phob!
Are you hurt? Did they do anything to you?
I'm fine.
Phob! Your blood?
Phob!
I'm fine.
You're safe now.
Thank you, Your Highness.
You should go.
But I think I should…
- I should drive you back to your palace.
- No, you can't.
I can go back tomorrow myself.
But right now, you should go.
- But..
- You should go.
Get home safe, okay?
Is everything okay? Did
you forget something?
No, I didn't.
I just think
that I should stay here with you.
It's totally fine, you should go.
- But it's dangerous…
- You need to go.
You need to leave.
Go!
Just go!
Leave me alone!
You need to go! Why did you come back?
Why can't I stay away from you?
I thought that if we never met again,
it would have been easier than this.
I could just see you in my dream.
I could just miss you.
Now you're standing right in front of me.
What do you expect me to do?
How do you expect me to forget you?
I used to think that way.
But no matter how long it takes,
I can never forget you.
My heart
always belongs to you.
And it will always belong to you
forever,
it will never change.
Hi,
you're up?
We shouldn't have done this, Phob.
You're right.
We shouldn't have done this.
But I will do this.
Phob!
Stop it.
Do you know
how long I've waited for this moment?
Phob.
Yeah?
I need to tell you something.
I heard about
people trying to transform
the national regime.
Have you ever heard of this?
What's the matter?
You can't be around these people.
It is dangerous
and you could be suspected.
Do you hear me?
Tin.
Dad?
Where have you been all night?
- I…
- About last night,
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize to me.
You've sacrificed your
happiness for the family's honor.
I shouldn't force you like that.
Instead, I should have
been more understanding.
From now on, I won't be involved
with your work anymore.
Dad?
Please forgive me.
Do you like the house?
Yeah.
Let's take a look inside.
This house belongs to Janthorn's relative.
It's for rent.
It is isolated.
Don't worry,
nobody can find us here.
We can meet here, what do you think?
If my dad finds out about this,
he will be so mad.
Take it one day at a time.
You know that my dad expects me
to take care of the palace.
He loves and worships his
family more than anything.
So he puts all the burden
on his son's shoulders?
Don't say that.
It is my job.
You may not have to bear the burden
all by yourself in the future.
What do you mean?
Well,
I mean that...
I can help with your burden
and I can help with the
thing that bothers you.
Sounds good?
I guess.
Now we have a cotton rose
tree at our house, Phob.
Phob!
- Come on, let me do it.
- No.
Just find something to
shield me from oil, hurry.
Put it down.
- Be careful.
- Phob!
Let me taste it.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
How is it?
- Is it good?
- It's good.
If you like it, then you should try this.
- So good.
- I knew it.
I think I cooked it so well. I'm so sure.
Among four dishes, which
one is your most favorite?
My most favorite?
I think it is…
That's enough.
Let me try.
- You think this is good?
- Yeah.
You sure?
My prince, come here.
- What is it?
- Come on, hurry.
- Hurry!
- It's here.
- Phob!
The cotton rose that
we planted is blooming.
Thin.
Yes?
Are you leaving the city again?
That's right.
Why do you have to
visit the country so often?
You've been gone for a month.
I'm not sure about that.
You should get going, I wont' disturb you.
See you later.
Do you think it will work?
Don't worry.
The students from France
planned the whole thing so well.
The national regime transformation
will get done easily.
What are they going to
do with the royal family?
They will be executed
and their assets will be confiscated.
Is that so?
Did the two soliders confess
about who ordered them?
Not yet, Your Highness.
But I contacted the head of
the police department already.
If they spilled the names of
their underground leaders,
the arrest warrant will be issued.
They were so drunk
and they spilled the plan.
They claimed that they were progressive
but they made a stupid mistake.
We need to tackle the root
of those who are trying to
change the national regime.
Commander General of Division 1
had been on the mission
to visit provinces in the south
since June 15.
During this time,
high-ranking soldiers
who are still in the city
including Ministry of
Defense' Deputy Chief of Staff,
Army Area Commander,
and Chief of Staff for the Royal Thai Army
are not staying in the city.
The members of royal
family are not in the city
so we can control the soldiers easier.
Oh my goodness!
The sources reported that the soldiers
from our side were arrested.
They were drunk and spilled our information
about trying to transform the nation.
What did you just say?
They didn't tell us yet
if it would be a warrant.
But soon
they will reveal the members
of this movement for sure.
Phob, we don't have that much time.
We need to do it.
The longer we wait,
the more information that
the other side will get.
We need to do something
to transform the nation.
Otherwise, we might
not have another chance.
[The King and Queen's schedule
to visit Klai Kangwong Palace.]
Phob? What are you looking for?
I…
Well…
I was looking for one of my papers.
In my briefcase?
I thought that perhaps
you would accidentally pick up my papers.
We've spent so much
time together constantly.
You're right.
That looks so good.
I brought you some snacks.
I'll clear it for you.
Come on, have a seat.
Here's your coffee.
Thank you.
Phob.
Where are you going?
Nowhere.
Did you heard the rumor
about a group trying
to transform the nation?
Two soldiers were
drunk and they revealed it.
I heard about it.
You need to be careful.
Don't ever be around that group.
My dad used to suspect you
and I didn't want you to be in danger.
Your Highness,
if one day,
I did something terrible to you,
would you forgive me?
Why are you asking me this?
I'm just worried
that it could be something
to upset you in the future.
And you would leave me because of it.
I don't want that day to come.
Listen to me,
if you don't leave me.
I won't leave you for sure.
When you were not
around, I was so tortured.
I won't let it happen again.
You're working for the army?
What kind of liquor did you drink?
You were so drunk and
said something so rebellious.
You shouldn't pay attention
to little things like that.
I told you already
that it was just a joke.
It is not real story.
Let's say that it was a joke,
like something you said among friends,
tell me, which friends would you discuss it with?
Do you want me to bring you to the palace
so you will give me names?
Do you want to see minister of the interior?
Tell me, who are working with you
in this disgraceful mission?
Tell me!
Write down the names.
You can still keep your head
attached to your shoulders,
I will tell them to lower your penalty.
They won't reveal anything.
I think we need to use harsher methods
to get them to speak.
They're so ungrateful to the nation.
I don't know what their plans are
but we need to be cautious.
Thinakorn is leaving the city quite often.
I'm worried about him.
What? The Royal Palace Office
doesn't have any work in the country lately.
None?
Well, I'm not sure.
Perhaps, they have to leave the city.
Otherwise, your son wouldn't tell you
that he needed to work in the country.
Phob!
It's not fair.
I was supposed to surprise you with it.
What?
Did you buy me a ring?
P T.
Phobthee.
Thinakorn.
Phob, do you like it?
I asked them to make it special for us.
Of course, I do.
I really like it.
Thank you so much.
Phob! Oh!
Phob.
(Next Episode )The two of us will
live like this, happy like this... forever.
I want to break off my
engagement with Ruethaisiri.
Pull yourself together, Phob! Is this why you
refused to extract information from Prince Thin?
We must execute the change of government
on Friday, June 24th.
Only two days left.
Two more days... Your
Highness, can you wait for me?
From now on, no matter what happens...
please know, Your Highness,
that I have never meant you any harm.
I have discovered
Prince Thin's whereabouts, Your Highness.